Finding Aid for Robert J. Harris papers, ca. 1959-ca. 1963 and 1969-1973
Bentley Historical Library, University of Michigan
- Newspaper clipping File
  - Alcoholism (Box 34)
  - Ann Arbor-Miscellaneous (Box 34)
  - Annexations (Box 34)
  - Appointments (Box 34)
  - Arboretum (Box 34)
  - Arts Committee (Box 34)
  - Assessment (Box 34)
  - Auto Lab Contract (Box 34)
  - Berlin Mayor Visit (Box 34)
  - Bicycles (Box 34)
  - Bird Hills Park (Box 34)
  - Black Action Movement (Box 34)
  - Black Community (Box 34)
  - Black Economic Development League (BEDL) (Box 34)
  - Blues Festival (Box 34)
  - Bonding Issues (Box 34)
  - Boundary Commission (New Ward Plans) (Box 34)
  - Briarwood Shopping Center (Box 34)
  - Budget (Box 34)
  - Building and Safety (Box 34)
  - Busses (Box 35)
  - Cable TV (Box 35)
  - Campus Inn (Box 35)
  - Capital Improvements (Box 35)
  - Census (Box 35)
  - Central Business District (Box 35)
  - Chamber of Commerce (Box 35)
  - Church Sit-Ins (Box 35)
  - City Hall-Miscellaneous (Box 35)
  - Civil Defense (Box 35)
  - Clerk (Box 35)
  - Committee for Economic Opportunity (CEO) (Box 35)
  - Community Renewal Program (CRP) (Box 35)
  - Consumer Protection (Box 35)
  - Contractors (Box 35)
  - Copernicus Committee (Box 35)
  - Council Briefs and Agendas (Box 35)
  - County Board of Supervisors (Box 35)
  - Courts (Box 36)
  - Day Care (Box 36)
  - Democratic Party (Box 36)
  - Dog Control (Box 36)
  - Drugs (Box 36)
  - Eighteen Year Old Vote (Box 36)
  - Eisenhower Parkway (Box 36)
  - Elections-Miscellaneous (Box 36)
  - Elections-County Millage September 1969 (Box 36)
  - Elections, City Council April, 1970 (Box 36)
  - Elections, General November 1970 (Box 36)
  - Elections, City Council April 1971 (Box 36)
  - Elections, City Council April, 1972 (Box 36)
  - Elections, General November 1972 (Box 36)
  - Elections-General November 1972 (Box 37)
  - Elections-City Council April 1973 (Box 37)
  - Employment (Box 37)
  - Environment (Box 37)
  - Esch, Marvin (U.S. Representative) (Box 37)
  - Fair Election Practices Committee (Box 37)
  - Farah Boycott (Box 37)
  - Federal Building (Box 37)
  - Fire Department (Box 37)
  - Flood insurance (Box 37)
  - Garden Homes Subdivision (Box 37)
  - Grievance Officer (Box 37)
  - Growth Policy (Box 37)
  - Gun Control (Box 37)
  - Halloween (Box 37)
  - Handicapped (Box 37)
  - Harmon, Samuel (Box 37)
  - Harris--PR file (Box 37)
  - Health (Box 37)
  - Historical Preservation (Box 38)
  - Hospital (Box 38)
  - Housing Commission (Box 38)
  - Housing Miscellaneous (Box 38)
  - Human Rights Commission (Box 38)
  - Human Rights Party (Box 38)
  - Huron High School (Box 38)
  - Huron River-Geddes Pond (Box 38)
  - Jail (Box 38)
  - Lansky's Junkyard (Box 38)
  - Legal Aid (Box 38)
  - Lettuce Boycott (Box 38)
  - Liquor Licenses (Box 38)
  - Maple Village Shopping Center (Box 38)
  - Market Committee (Box 38)
  - Massage Parlors (Box 38)
  - Mental health (Box 38)
  - Michigan-Miscellanea (Box 38)
  - Mill Creek Park (Box 38)
  - Model Cities (Box 39)
  - Municipal League (Box 39)
  - Murders (and John Norman Collins trial) (Box 39)
  - Nixon, Richard M. (Box 39)
  - Noise (Box 39)
  - Non-returnable bottles (Box 39)
  - Obscenity (Box 39)
  - Office of Economic Opportunity (OEO) (Box 39)
  - Ozone House (Box 39)
  - Parental Responsibility (Box 39)
  - Parking and Traffic (Box 39)
  - Parks and Recreation (Box 39)
  - Peace Movement (Box 39)
  - Planning (Box 39)
  - Police (Box 40)
  - Political Groups (Box 40)
  - Precinct Delegate Election (Box 40)
  - Proclamations (Box 40)
  - Protests (Box 40)
  - Public Works (Box 40)
  - Radical Independent Party (Box 40)
  - Railroads (Box 40)
  - Rainbow People's Party (Box 40)
  - Recall Campaign (Box 40)
  - Rent and Rent Control (Box 40)
  - Rent Strike (Box 40)
  - Revenue Sharing (Box 40)
  - Schools (Box 41)
  - Schulers' Project (Box 41)
  - Senior Citizens (Box 41)
  - Sesquicentennial (Box 41)
  - Sex Discrimination (Box 41)
  - Sheraton Hotel (Box 41)
  - Sheriff (Box 41)
  - Sign Ordinance (Box 41)
  - Sister Cities (Box 41)
  - Snow Storm (1973) (Box 41)
  - Southeast Michigan Council of Governments (SEMCOG) (Box 41)
  - Street Fair (Box 41)
  - South University Disturbances (1969) (Box 41)
  - Summit Street Medical Center (Box 41)
  - Sunday Rock Concerts (Box 41)
  - Taxes (Box 41)
  - Taxi Cabs (Box 41)
  - Third Party (Box 41)
  - Topless Dancing (Box 41)
  - Traffic and Parking (Box 42)
  - Trains (Box 42)
  - Transportation (Box 42)
  - Unions (Box 42)
  - Unit Pricing (Box 42)
  - United Fund (Box 42)
  - United Nations Day (Box 42)
  - University (Box 42)
  - Utilities (Box 42)
  - Veterans (Box 42)
  - Washtenaw Neighborhood (Box 42)
  - Welfare (Box 42)
  - West Park Troubles (Box 42)
  - Women (Box 42)
  - Workable Program (Box 42)
  - Youth (Box 42)
  - Miscellaneous (Box 42)
- Miscellaneous Files
  - Proclamations 1969-1970 (Box 43)
  - Letters of Congratulations (Box 43)
  - Ceremonials (Box 43)
  - Papers concerning Sunday Rock Concerts 1969 (Box 43)
  - Papers concerning the South University disturbances 1969, 4 folders (Box 43)
- Law School
  - Course and research materials circa 1959-1963 (Box 44)